{
    "levels":
    [
        {
            "level": 1,
            "levelUp": 3,
            "problems":
            [
                {
                    "problem": "15 + 9",
                    "solution": 24
                },
                {
                    "problem": "20 + 2",
                    "solution": 22
                },
                {
                    "problem": "11 + 1",
                    "solution": 12
                },
                {
                    "problem": "5 + 6",
                    "solution": 11
                },
                {
                    "problem": "4 + 2",
                    "solution": 6
                },
                {
                    "problem": "9 + 10",
                    "solution": 19
                },
                {
                    "problem": "80 + 1",
                    "solution": 81
                },
                {
                    "problem": "9 + 90",
                    "solution": 99
                },
                {
                    "problem": "8 + 9",
                    "solution": 17
                },
                {
                    "problem": "8 + 10",
                    "solution": 18
                },
                {
                    "problem": "17 + 9",
                    "solution": 26
                },
                {
                    "problem": "16 + 9",
                    "solution": 25
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": 2,
            "levelUp": 12,
            "problems":
            [
                {
                    "problem": "176 - 33",
                    "solution": 143
                },
                {
                    "problem": "94 - 28",
                    "solution": 66
                },
                {
                    "problem": "11 - 4",
                    "solution": 7
                },
                {
                    "problem": "78 - 37",
                    "solution": 41
                },
                {
                    "problem": "97 - 30",
                    "solution": 67
                },
                {
                    "problem": "51 - 10",
                    "solution": 41
                },
                {
                    "problem": "15 - 5",
                    "solution": 10
                },
                {
                    "problem": "65 - 23",
                    "solution": 42
                },
                {
                    "problem": "70 - 9",
                    "solution": 61
                },
                {
                    "problem": "8 - 5",
                    "solution": 3
                },
                {
                    "problem": "17 - 11",
                    "solution": 6
                },
                {
                    "problem": "70 - 35",
                    "solution": 35
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": 3,
            "levelUp": 100,
            "problems":
            [
                {
                    "problem": "DEMO",
                    "solution": -1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}